

Chukwudebelu Ojijieme

Sales Consultant



Professional Summary

Highly motivated sales professional offering progressive sales and marketing experience. Highly results-oriented and energetic with unsurpassed interpersonal and communication strengths.

Productive, hardworking and known for consistent stellar performance against target sales goals and customer service expectations.



Work History

2021-02 -Current

Trainer/ Facilitator / Coach

Web Of Hearts Foundation, Bogije, Lagos State

- Scheduled and taught in class and online courses to increase learning opportunities.
- Quickly adapted training plans for client needs, keeping timelines and desires in mind.
- Developed individualized plans to help participants reach goals within predetermined timelines.
- Recorded and edited videos for use in later courses or by remote learners.
- Assess student needs to develop effective training plans.
- Track attendance and progress against goals for each participant.
- Perform continuous evaluations of content and plans in order to enhance delivery and improve effectiveness.
- Gathered and organized supplementary material to support structured lessons.



Address

Bogije, Lagos State, 100176

Phone

08142690783

E-mail

cdbojijieme@gmail.com



Coaching and training



Excellent

Outstanding communication and interpersonal skills



Leadership skills



Excellent

Flexible & Adaptable



Conflict resolution



Current

Expert

GOPA Worldwide Consultant, Lekki, Lagos

- Training and Coaching IOM beneficiaries with the aim of improving their entrepreneurial skills through a specialized entrepreneurship training for returning migrants, especially returning from Germany.
- Quickly adapted training plans for client needs, keeping timelines, budgets and desires in mind.
- Performed continuous evaluations of content and plans in order to enhance delivery and improve effectiveness.

2020-11 -2021-10

Sales Consultant

Wilsons Juice Co. LTD., Lekki, Lagos

- Cold called and conducted face-to-face sales calls with C-level executives and directors in assigned sales territory.
- Created detailed sales presentations to communicate product features and market data.
- Followed up with existing customers to provide additional support and address any concerns.
- Completed orders and organized product deliveries to meet customer timetables.
- Used consultative sales approach to understand customer needs and recommend relevant offerings.
- Used prospecting and client development techniques to produce fresh leads and maintain solid conversion rate.

2019-11 -2020-03

Facilities Manager

Property Owners Group, Lekki, Lagos

- Accounted for building usage and organizational needs when planning maintenance activities.
- Controlled expenses to meet budget requirements.
- Created sustainable improvement initiatives for efficient use of energy.
- Investigated problems and determined appropriate remedies.

- Drove continuous improvement of processes and systems operation.
- Oversaw all aspects of equipment installation, maintenance, and repair for both internal and external services.
- Conducted daily inspections of facility grounds, external structure, systems, and equipment.

2019-06 -2019-11

Business Development Executive

Neodym 7 International Ltd, Lekki, Lagos

- Developed and executed strategic initiatives to implement key changes and improvements in business development and sales programs.
- Developed short-term and long-term sales objectives and strategic plans to meet market needs.
- Evaluated current service needs and product satisfaction levels with established customers.
- Planned marketing initiatives and leveraged referral network to promote business development.
- Created strategic and tactical sales initiatives for forward planning to meet key objectives.
- Fostered and facilitated relationships with product distribution channels to increase product sales.
- Conducted cold- calls to prospect external lead sources and advance sales process.



Education

20121 - 2017-01

BSc.: Finance

University of Lagos - Lagos, Nigeria

- Coursework in Corporate Finance, Investment Analysis & Portfolio Management and Cost accounting
- Thesis: Impact of Financial Institutions on Agriculture (A case study of Commercial Banks)



Certifications